When his world was stolen, Mark Hogancamp made a world of his own.
Marwencol is a documentary film directed by Jeff Malmberg.
After a vicious attack leaves him brain-damaged and broke, Mark Hogancamp seeks recovery in
"Marwencol", a 1/6th scale World War II-era town he creates in his backyard.
Self, played by Mark Hogancamp.
Self, played by Emmanuel Nneji.
Self, played by Edda Hogancamp.
Self, played by Tom Neubauer.
Self, played by Julie Swarthout.
Self, played by Janet Wikane.
Marwencol (also known as Village of the Dolls in the UK) is a 2010 American documentary film
that explores the life and work of artist and photographer Mark Hogancamp.
It is the debut feature of director Jeff Malmberg, produced
through his production company Open Face.
It was the inspiration for Welcome to Marwen, a 2018
drama directed by Robert Zemeckis.